<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="generating">Génération de vos informations locales...</string>

    <string name="app_name" >CypherSend</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Paramètres</string>
    <string name="action_update">Télécharger les messages</string>
    <string name="action_guided">Guide</string>

    <string name="app_cypher_and_send">Envoyer par le serveur</string>
    <string name="app_cypher_and_apps">Envoyer via une application tierce</string>

    <string name="share_popup">Partagez un message avec une autre application</string>
    <string name="discution_popup">Discutions ou messages jetables avec les amis utilisant le serveur</string>
    <string name="vault_popup">Nothing here... for now ;)</string>

    <!-- main interface string definition-->
    <string name="main_send">Partage de vos informations publiques</string>
    <string name="main_web_send">Envoyer un message par web</string>
    <string name="main_share_send">Envoyer par une application tierce</string>

    <string name="main_send_no_friends_title">Erreur</string>
    <string name="main_send_no_friends_message">Vous n\'avez pas d\'amis enregistrés. Demandez leur de vous envoyer les informations publiques, scannez les puis retentez.</string>

    <string name="follow_me">Suivre @codlab</string>

    <string name="personnal_data_subject">Partage de mes informations publiques</string>
    <string name="personnal_data_subject_third_party">Partage d\'un message chiffré avec vos informations</string>

    <string name="select_the_device_to_send_to">Choisissez l\'ami à qui envoyer le message</string>
    <string name="select_the_device_to_send_to_and_share">Select the recipient device and you will then be able to use any Android\'s app to share the encrypted message</string>
    <string name="share_via">Partager par</string>
    <string name="action_share">Partager</string>

    <string name="title_section_default">Accueil</string>
    <string name="title_section_friends">Amis</string>
    <string name="title_section_web">Web</string>
    <string name="title_section_help">Aide</string>

    <string name="no_intent">Merci de sélectionner un autre moyen de partage</string>

    <string name="no_friends">Vous n\'avez actuellement aucun amis sur cet appareil.</string>
    <string name="guided_tour_1">Use this application to share private messages with your Android device !</string>
    <string name="guided_tour_1_shortcut"></string>
    <string name="guided_tour_2">First step is to share your public information with some friends. These information look like a simple URL. Tell them to click on it while having the app installed.</string>
    <string name="guided_tour_3">Ask your friends for their own public information. You will receive urls you will need to click on to add theirs on your device.</string>
    <string name="guided_tour_4">Every secret message you will send are signed with your own information, exactly the same for your friends. You can know they sent them.</string>
    <string name="guided_tour_5">Take care of messages from unknown person, but don\'t be paranoid, it\'s unlikely a virus will arrive :p</string>
    <string name="guided_tour_6">Use your own chat apps, emails, etc... to send messages to your friends! Don\'t stop using them!</string>
    <string name="guided_tour_7">You also can subscribe to servers to manage your messages for you. In the settings, set your device name, ask to register on the server and you are ready to receive messages! The message are AUTOMATICALLY erased when you retrieve them! NO messages are stored, you don\'t trust me? Next slide ;)</string>
    <string name="guided_tour_8">You can create your own server : it is Open Source, then simply edit your settings to add its URL and finally share your public information with your friends, they will then send (not read) messages to the server</string>
    <string name="help_part_1_title">Register device for server side transactions</string>
    <string name="help_part_1_content">Registering your device is very easy BUT ABSOLUTELY NOT THE MOST IMPORTANT THING TO DO. \n First of all, open the settings via the menu and set your device name (remember the fact to stay anonymous). Then set the server url if you use your own server. Remember to register the device to the server (in order to retrieve your messages from it).\nAnd.... it\'s done. You\'re ready to receive messages (use the refresh button from the Actionbar).\nNote that you can also receive push notifications from Google (the GCM) by using the default server AND accepting to receive push notifications. pros and cons about these things are in the last part of this document.</string>
    <string name="help_part_2_title">Share your public information</string>
    <string name="help_part_2_content">Don\'t forget to send to your friend your device public data : you can use Android Beam to share them OR use the button on the main screen to send them via a third party app.\nOnce done, make sure your friend has your device name in his devices list from the second tab</string>
    <string name="help_part_3_title">Send message to friend\'s device</string>
    <string name="help_part_3_content">Two way to send a message.\nThe first one is to select the device of your friend in the second tab and select it. Then type your message and validate. Your friend can now retrieve the message from the server.\n \nSecond possibility, when you are in a browser, mail etc... select the message to send, and choose the share option from them. You will see the icon of the app with the title you can send the message to a device server. Select this one (not the other one) and validate the device of your friend. Once again, validate and it\'s done.</string>
    <string name="help_part_4_title">Send an encrypted message to a device via third party apps</string>
    <string name="help_part_4_content">Last but not the least. The app also permits you to transfer from an app, a message, text etc... encrypt it and then select an app to transfer the desired message.\nTo do so, select a text in an app and then use the share option from it.\nLocate the app icon in the list with the title indicating the use of third party app\nThen select your friend device, and click on the button on the right of it to send the encrypted message\nFinally, select the final app to send this encrypted message. Your friend will now be able to receive the encrypted message from his mail, etc...</string>
    <string name="help_part_5_title">Notes</string>
    <string name="help_part_5_content">Public infos are bounded to a device, not user so... when you change your device, you need to backup the information of your device if you want to restore/copy them to the new device.Warning : doing so will create a file on your sdcard (export.zip), you absolutely need to keep it secret, even if it is password protected, you can never trust any apps or anybody (even me and my apps...).\nUsing the force registering in the options will reset and create new public/private infos so your friends could not be able to send you messages you can unencrypt - remember to warn them\nIf you have multiple devices, you will be able to unencrypt a message only with the specified device! Not the other ones\n\n Remember that the app was supposed to be used to keep privacy... so the sharing options are not supposed to be here to let you keep encrypted message, ensure to delete the mail/sms/everything which carried the message when read! Obviously, when you use the server update messages, the message are deleted server-side WHEN you retrieve them!</string>
    <string name="help_part_7_title">ProTips</string>
    <string name="help_part_7_content">Never trust anybody you don\'t know when you receive a message.\nNever give someon the export.zip file or ALL your keys! Since the private key is obviously a key to keep secret - anyone with your keys will be able to send message and tell anyone he is yourself! Also the real time messenger available via GCM+my server is to use at your own risk.\n\nNote that when you use the GCM, Google will be able to know you possibly received a new content notification but will never be able to decode it since the encrypted information never pass through their servers.\nYou can obviously use the third party apps to be used as proxy, but remember that companies often only needs your metadata from your data : here it can be 1/ when did you send/receive a message. 2/ how long was the encrypted message! 3/ With who did you share the message?</string>
    <string name="help_part_6_title">Contact</string>
    <string name="help_part_6_content">You can contact me directly here:\nmail : codlabtech@gmail.com\ntwitter : http://twitter.com/codlab \nweb in general : search for codlab B)\n</string>

    <string name="not_suppose_to_be_this_device">Le message ne semble pas être destiné à votre appareil. (erreur de clés)</string>

    <string name="device_send_message">Nouveau message partagé</string>
    <string name="device_web_send_message">Nouveau message web</string>

    <string name="settings_device_title">Nom de cet appareil</string>
    <string name="settings_device_summary">Il sera envoyé à vos amis pour vous identifier rapidement</string>

    <string name="settings_website_title">Website root/url</string>
    <string name="settings_website_summary">The website url with / (!) to use as root to retrieve new messages</string>

    <string name="settings_register_title">Enregistrement sur le serveur</string>
    <string name="settings_register_summary">Vous enregistrer permet à vos amis de vous envoyer des messages directement par le web</string>

    <string name="settings_force_title">Force whole new registering</string>
    <string name="settings_force_summary">Will generate new devices info AND link to the server. Use to force register - you will need to resend to your friend your data</string>


    <string name="user_category">Utilisateur</string>
    <string name="server_state_category">Serveur</string>

    <string name="device">device</string>
    <string name="website">website</string>
    <string name="identifier">identifier</string>
    <string name="pass">pass</string>
    <string name="register">register</string>
    <string name="register_force">register_force</string>
    <string name="gcm_settings">gcm</string>

    <string name="default_server">https://cypher.codlab.eu/</string>

    <string name="dialog_message_register_title">Enregistrement web</string>
    <string name="dialog_message_register_message_ok">Vous avez été enregistré avec succès!</string>
    <string name="dialog_message_register_message_ko">Le serveur n\'a pas accepté votre requête : l\'appareil est déjà enregistré?</string>
    <string name="dialog_message_register_message_timeout">Le serveur n\'est pas accessible.</string>

    <string name="dialog_message_force_title">Force new register</string>
    <string name="dialog_message_force_message_ok">The new register is ok. Please resend to your friend the data!</string>
    <string name="dialog_message_force_message_ko">The server did not accept the info : correct server?</string>

    <string name="successfully_saved">Sauvegarde effectuée avec succès</string>
    <string name="error_saved">Erreur lors de la récupération de nouvelles valeurs</string>
    <string name="successfully_shared">Partagé avec succès</string>

    <string name="dialog_message_received_title">Nouveau message reçu</string>
    <string name="dialog_message_received_title_error">Erreur message</string>
    <string name="dialog_message_received_message">Message de A : \nB</string>
    <string name="dialog_message_received_content_error_decypher">Un message n\'a pas pu être déchiffré :(</string>
    <string name="dialog_message_received_content_error_null">Une exception est survenue pendant la récupération des messages. Est-ce que le réseau est actif? Etes-vous enregistrés?</string>
    <string name="dialog_message_received_title_empty">Aucun message</string>
    <string name="dialog_message_received_content_empty">Aucune message n\'a été trouvé sur le serveur</string>

    <string name="dialog_message_send_title">Statut de l\'émission</string>
    <string name="dialog_message_send_content_ok">Votre message a été envoyé avec succès sur le serveur</string>
    <string name="dialog_message_send_content_error">Une erreur est survenue pendant l\'émission du message</string>

    <string name="ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="yes">Oui</string>
    <string name="no">Non</string>

    <string name="help_send">Utilisez le mode messagerie pour échanger vos messages persistents/éphémères in-app avec vos amis. Envoyez leur d\'abord vos infos publiques !</string>
    <string name="help_share">Utilisez le mode partage pour utiliser n\'importe quelle application à vos amis. Envoyez leur d\'abord vos infos publiques !</string>

    <string name="no_messages">Vous n\'avez ni reçu ni envoyé de messages. Commencez dès maintenant en envoyant à votre correspondant vos informations publiques.</string>

    <string name="dialog_request_send_title">Envoyer un message</string>
    <string name="dialog_request_send_message">Veuillez indiquer le texte que vous voulez ensuite par une application tierce</string>
    <string name="dialog_request_send_message_web">Veuillez indiquer le message texte que vous voulez envoyer en passant par le serveur du destinataire</string>

    <string name="known_sender">Message envoyé par %s.\n</string>
    <string name="unknown_sender">Message envoyé par un utilisateur inconnu.\n</string>

    <string name="gcm_title">Nouveau messages dans le cloud</string>
    <string name="gcm_message">Quelqu\'un vient de vous envoyer un message. Cliquez ici pour lancer l\'application et charger les messages web.</string>

    <string name="settings_gcm_title">Notifications Push</string>
    <string name="settings_gcm_summary">Acceptation des notifications push</string>
    <string name="settings_gcm_summary_on">Vous serez notifiés en temps réel.</string>
    <string name="settings_gcm_summary_off">Aucune notification.</string>

    <string name="no_info_title">Oups! Paramètres par défaut détectés</string>
    <string name="no_info_text">Vous utilisez les paramètres par défaut. Il est conseillé de configurer l\'application. Voulez-vous éditer les paramètres?</string>

    <string name="gcm_acceptance">Acceptez-vous les notifications push? Google n\'est présent que pour indiquer à votre appareil que de nouveaux messages existent. C\'est par la suite que l\'appareil contacte "directement" le serveur.</string>

    <string name="keys_export_title">Exportez vos clés</string>
    <string name="keys_export_message">Exporte vos clés dans /sdcard/keys.zip</string>

    <string name="keys_import_title">Importez vos clés</string>
    <string name="keys_import_message">Importez les clés. Le fichier /sdcard/keys.zip doit exister. Il sera effacé!</string>

    <string name="keys_import">keys_import</string>
    <string name="keys_export">keys_export</string>

    <string name="keys_import_export">Gérer vos informations</string>

    <string name="keys_input_export">Définissez un mot de passe pour exporter vos clés</string>
    <string name="keys_input_import">Quel est le mot de passe de l\'archive?</string>
    <string name="keys_import_error">Erreur pendant l\'importation. Archive existante? Mot de passe correct?</string>

    <string name="error">Erreur !</string>

    <string name="restart_app_title">Informations enregistrées</string>
    <string name="restart_app_message">L\'application nécessite d\'être redémarrée. CLiquez sur OK pour relancer l\'app automatiquement.</string>

    <string name="bitcoin_donate">Faire une donation bitcoin</string>

    <string name="name_title">Nom de l\'appareil</string>
    <string name="name_message">Quel est le nom de votre appareil?</string>

    <string name="gcm_register_title">Notifications Push</string>
    <string name="gcm_register_message">Voulez-vous recevoir des notifications de nouveau contenu?</string>

    <string name="register_title">Service en ligne</string>
    <string name="register_message">Enregistrement sur le serveur web? (recevoir des messages par le web)</string>

    <string name="register_password_title">Mot de passe</string>
    <string name="register_password_message">Définir un mot de passe pour le service en ligne</string>

    <string name="codlab_public">Ajouter les infos de @codlab</string>
    <string name="vault_title">Coffre sécurisé</string>
    <string name="no_pin">Vous n\'avez pas de code pin configuré. Veuillez vous diriger dans les paramètres pour en définir un. Notez qu\'actuellement, seule l\'aide sera affichée ;)</string>
    <string name="add_note">Ajouter une nouvelle note</string>
    <string name="note_empty">Vous n\'avez actuellement aucune note sur cet appareil. Notez qu\'actuellement, seule l\'aide sera affichée ;)</string>
    <string name="note_name">Nom</string>
    <string name="note_content">Contenu</string>
    <string name="note_cancel">Annuler</string>
    <string name="note_confirm">Ajouter</string>
    <string name="note_remove">Effacer</string>
    <string name="note_copy">Copier</string>

    <string name="note_help">Each note can be copy to your clipboard. Incoming : copy note from whatever apps you are into!</string>


    <string name="vault_category">Paramètres coffre-fort</string>
    <string name="pin_modify_title">Modifier le pin</string>
    <string name="pin_modify_message">Un pin doit être inséré pour accèder au coffre fort</string>
    <string name="keys_vault">vault</string>

    <string name="decode_error_maybe_invalid">Une erreur est survenue pendant le déchiffrement du message. Etes-vous certains d\'être destinataire du message?\n\nSi vous connaissez l\'émetteur, contactez-le afin de le prévenir que vous avez certainement changé vos informations publiques et qu\'il doive les mettre à jour.\n\nSi jamais l\'erreur persiste, vous pouvez contacter le développeur sur codlabtech@gmail.com\n\nVeuillez excuser pour la gêne occasionnée</string>

    <string name="progress_dialog_load_messages_title">Messages web</string>
    <string name="progress_dialog_load_messages_message">Téléchargement de messages depuis le serveur</string>

    <string name="incognito_on">Les messages s\'autodétruiront</string>
    <string name="incognito_off">Les messages seront sauvegardés sur les appareils</string>

    <string name="message_was_incognito">Le message n\'a pas été sauvegardé car il était en mode incognito</string>
    <string name="message_was_not_incognito">Le message a été sauvegardé</string>
    <string name="orbot_running">Orbot fonctionne. Les communications passent par un chiffrement habituel ainsi que le réseau Tor .</string>
    <string name="orbot_not_running">Orbot ne fonctionne pas. Les communications passent par un canal chiffré et sécurisé normal.</string>
    <string name="orbot_not_installed">Orbot n\'est pas installé. Seul le chiffrement des communications sera assuré.</string>
    <string name="orbot_activate">Activer Orbot</string>
    <string name="orbot_install">Installer Orbot</string>
</resources>
